https://idsticker.com/privacy-policy

AssetGuard LLC’s Privacy Policy – An Overview
AssetGuard LLC is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers. We are committed to providing a safe and secure environment for our customers.
The purpose of this AssetGuard LLC privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit us, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Please note that this policy applies only to AssetGuard LLC and websites that carry the AssetGuard LLC brand, and not to other companies or organizations’ websites to which we link. We have clearly marked AssetGuard LLC and these branded web sites with our company name so you know where this policy applies.
Information About All AssetGuard LLC Visitors
In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to AssetGuard LLC and its areas. This data helps us determine how much our customers use different parts of the site. For example, AssetGuard LLC uses “cookies” that tell us how and when pages on our site are visited, and by how many people.
Information About You
We may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service or when you order a product. We will need certain information — such as name, e-mail address, billing address, credit card number — in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information by modifying your settings on your members page, or by contacting us via email. You may modify or delete any information AssetGuard LLC has about you by contacting us. We do not sell or share your email address with third parties without your express consent to “opt-in” to receive additional information from third parties.
Database Access
Our registration database is a restricted access zone, strictly limited only to individuals who have fulfilled internal security checks.
AssetGuard LLC Privacy Policy Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy for AssetGuard LLC, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.
Setup AccountAbout UsContact UsFAQPrivacy Policy
MENU
Home
Member Home
Report Found
Purchase IDsticker
Register
